A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Secretary's Office, Biographical Files, RG 15 FA1280
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Staff, A-Z, 1958-1971; 3; 9.2 Cubic Feet 7 record storage boxes
  - Merna, Elizabeth F., 1968 March 29 (Box 38)
  - Meyer, Mary Lois, 1971 September 30 (Box 38)
  - Middleton, Eleanor, 1961 December 15 (Box 38)
  - Migliore, Pat, 1969 February 7 (Box 38)
  - Miller, Alice, 1971 March 12 (Box 38)
  - Miller, Jarjorie M., 1967 October 31 (Box 38)
  - Miller, Perry, 1963 October 31 (Box 38)
  - Mills, Junius C., 1961 August 25 (Box 38)
  - Mitchell, Jeanette, 1964 January 15 (Box 38)
  - Moed, Helen M., 1963 October 11 (Box 38)
  - Moeller, Elsa P., 1965 July 9 (Box 38)
  - Montanez, Judy, 1968 May 28 (Box 38)
  - Montevago, Peter J., 1967 March 8 (Box 38)
  - Moody, Sandra L., 1966 September 2 (Box 38)
  - Moore, Andrea, 1968 August 30 (Box 38)
  - Moore, G. Katherine, 1968 May 31 (Box 38)
  - Moreback, Rose, 1968 September 13 (Box 38)
  - Morgan, Jesse, 1961 September 20 (Box 38)
  - Morrow, Lynn B., 1970 September 2 (Box 38)
  - Mortensen, Faith E., 1969 September 1 (Box 38)
  - Moss, Melvin, 1961 July 14 (Box 38)
  - Moussette, Josephine C., 1960 January 8 (Box 38)
  - Mueller, Ruth, 1963 January 25 (Box 38)
  - Mullins, Curtis J., 1962 April 27 (Box 38)
  - Munoz, Maria Elena, 1970 April 17 (Box 38)
  - Musarra, Frank J., 1963 February 8 (Box 38)
  - Naggar, Yahya, 1971 October 29 (Box 39)
  - Naigles, Lora, 1961 September 19 (Box 39)
  - Nelson, Lennox M., 1967 February 15 (Box 39)
  - Neuer, Doris, 1970 June 30 (Box 39)
  - Neuman, Edna, 1964 June 30 (Box 39)
  - Nevilis, Martha, 1969 August 8 (Box 39)
  - Newman, Alan Harvey, 1963 September 13 (Box 39)
  - Newnham, Celia, 1963 April 23 (Box 39)
  - Newsome, Benjamin, 1968 January 30 (Box 39)
  - Newsome, Lois S., 1966 January 11 (Box 39)
  - Newton, Alan, 1971 August 27 (Box 39)
  - Newton, Virginia, 1965 August 18 (Box 39)
  - Nielson, Mark, 1971 August 20 (Box 39)
  - Noonan, Helen, 1969 May 29 (Box 39)
  - Northrup, Linda, 1969 June 13 (Box 39)
  - Norton, James, 1970 August 10 (Box 39)
  - Noten, Irene, 1964 March 23 (Box 39)
  - Novak, Sheila, 1969 September 5 (Box 39)
  - Nussbaum, Hedda, 1969 September 10 (Box 39)
  - O'Connell, Beatrice, 1965 June 30 (Box 39)
  - O'Connell, Francis, 1967 April 7 (Box 39)
  - Odabashian, Betty G., 1965 September 15 (Box 39)
  - Ogden, Joan, 1963 August 30 (Box 39)
  - O'Hea, Patricia, 1968 April 19 (Box 39)
  - Ojala, Elaine, 1962 March 14 (Box 39)
  - O'Keefe, Evelyn, 1971 April 9 (Box 39)
  - Olson, Irene T., 1961 June 7 (Box 39)
  - O'Neill, Ileana, 1969 January 17 (Box 39)
  - O'Neill, Patricia, 1962 December 31 (Box 39)
  - Oshinski, Carolyn, 1971 June 30 (Box 39)
  - Ostrove, Leslie, 1969 July 30 (Box 39)
  - O'Sullivan, Thomas, 1971 January 31 (Box 39)
  - Owen, Elizabeth, 1966 December 31 (Box 39)
  - Padgett, Karen, 1969 August 8 (Box 39)
  - Parenteau, Janice, 1968 August 30 (Box 39)
  - Paris, Zoe, 1963 June 14 (Box 39)
  - Parrott, Janice, 1961 October 24 (Box 39)
  - Parry, Louise, 1964 April 14 (Box 39)
  - Pasternosto, Cesar, 1971 June 23 (Box 39)
  - Paternosto, Maria, 1970 April 13 (Box 39)
  - Patterson, Constance, 1961 December 22 (Box 39)
  - Paul, Helen M. (Box 39)
  - Peacock, Martha, 1969 October 15 (Box 39)
  - Pereira, Ana A., 1970 September 11 (Box 39)
  - Perez, Robert, 1966 May 20 (Box 39)
  - Perlman, Don, 1963 June 24 (Box 39)
  - Perlman, Priscilla, 1964 August 31 (Box 39)
  - Peterson, Janet, 1965 September 30 (Box 39)
  - Petterson, Georgette B., 1966 January 28 (Box 39)
  - Pettinelli, Frances, 1969 March 14 (Box 39)
  - Pfeffer, Larry M., 1969 July 17 (Box 39)
  - Phillips, Margaret, 1968 May 31 (Box 39)
  - Phillips, Oruille, 1961 April 24 (Box 39)
  - Philips, Sally, 1965 December 30 (Box 39)
  - Pichon, Erlinda, 1968 October 18 (Box 39)
  - Pineda, Rafael, 1971 December 24 (Box 39)
  - Pleasants, Elizabeth, 1969 November 26 (Box 39)
  - Plimpton, Nancy, 1964 April 24 (Box 39)
  - Pober, Marianne, 1971 August 13 (Box 39)
  - Poetzl, Joyce, 1968 April 12 (Box 39)
  - Polatsek, Esther, 1969 August 1 (Box 39)
  - Poletsky, Marilyn, 1965 August 27 (Box 39)
  - Pomerantz, Ellen, 1969 June 6 (Box 39)
  - Pomerantz, Judy, 1969 August 27 (Box 39)
  - Post, Barbara, 1964 November 30 (Box 39)
  - Prensky, Catherine, 1963 June 21 (Box 39)
  - Price, Joseph Eugene, 1971 December 31 (Box 39)
  - Price, Maria Helena, 1969 May 31 (Box 39)
  - Pritchard, Alma, 1964 May 28 (Box 39)
  - Pullins, Press, 1968 August 21 (Box 39)
  - Rabinowitz, Evelyn, 1968 June 21 (Box 39)
  - Racle, Robert, 1967 February 3 (Box 39)
  - Radin, Helen, 1963 August 30 (Box 39)
  - Radow, Vera, 1969 June 5 (Box 39)
  - Ramirez, John, 1967 May 26 (Box 39)
  - Ramskill, Donna, 1966 May 20 (Box 39)
  - Raskin, Roslyn, 1966 May 20 (Box 39)
  - Rebecci, Claire, 1966 September 2 (Box 39)
  - Reckling, Richard, 1970 September 28 (Box 39)
  - Redd, John L., 1967 May 23 (Box 39)
  - Rednauer, Dennis C., 1964 December 4 (Box 39)
  - Renz, Enid, 1968 June 1 (Box 39)
  - Resch, Joseph, 1966 September 30 (Box 39)
  - Resnick, Bar-ara E., 1967 June 29 (Box 39)
  - Reynolds, David R., 1970 March 16 (Box 39)
  - Reynolds, Suzanne P., 1967 January 31 (Box 39)
  - Rich, Linda, 1966 January 28 (Box 39)
  - Richards, Robin, 1967 August 24 (Box 39)
  - Richey, Merle, 1966 June 8 (Box 39)
  - Riuoire, Anne C., 1963 September 20 (Box 39)
  - Robinson, Victor, 1967 November 10 (Box 39)
  - Roman, Carol, 1966 August 26 (Box 39)
  - Rojas, Barbara, 1967 June 7 (Box 39)
  - Roller, Barbara, 1967 September 15 (Box 39)
  - Rosen, David, 1967 September 15 (Box 40)
  - Rubin, Marjorie, 1965 February 26 (Box 40)
  - Rubottom, Eleanor, 1964 September 4 (Box 40)
  - Rugg, Margaret, 1968 July 31 (Box 40)
  - Rush, Lawrence, 1962 January 12 (Box 40)
  - Rush, Raymond V., 1962 September 7 (Box 40)
  - Russak, Debbie I., 1961 March 17 (Box 40)
  - Russo, Trudy, 1967 June 30 (Box 40)
  - Sa, Sophie, 1964 September 4 (Box 40)
  - Sabato, Vicky, 1967 September 22 (Box 40)
  - Sachs, Randy Lee, 1965 April 15 (Box 40)
  - Sahut, Gisele, 1970 February 6 (Box 40)
  - Saied, Jamelia, 1969 June 13 (Box 40)
  - St. Pierre, Ronald, 1972-1975 (Box 40)
  - Salcedo, Michael, 1964 May 29 (Box 40)
  - Salvesen, Linda A., 1971 November 5 (Box 40)
  - Samala, Franklin, 1966 January 31 (Box 40)
  - Sambat, Thomas, 1967 March 7 (Box 40)
  - Samuel, Willie, 1965 November 5 (Box 40)
  - Sanchez, Hector, 1969 July 18 (Box 40)
  - Santiago, Blanca, 1969 May 29 (Box 40)
  - Sapiro, Cornelia, 1969 July 4 (Box 40)
  - Sarauia, Marietta, 1964 July 31 (Box 40)
  - Saunders, Horace, 1966 April 12 (Box 40)
  - Saums, Dorothy, 1968 January 19 (Box 40)
  - Savedge, Suzanne, 1966 May 31 (Box 40)
  - Savides, Thalia, 1970 January 30 (Box 40)
  - Savitz, Laura R., 1966 June 30 (Box 40)
  - Schiele, Margaret, 1964 July 31 (Box 40)
  - Schin, Theresa, 1961 March 2 (Box 40)
  - Schramm, Barbara M., 1962 August 31 (Box 40)
  - Schulze, Darrell, 1969 September 19 (Box 40)
  - Schumka, Sandra, 1967 February 11 (Box 40)
  - Schwind, John, 1963 June 7 (Box 40)
  - Siedman, Eleanor, 1962 December 28 (Box 40)
  - Selgas, Manuel, 1965 July 16 (Box 40)
  - Sevier, Mary Jane, 1968 August 23 (Box 40)
  - Shabad, Goldie, 1968 September 11 (Box 40)
  - Shaff, Susan, 1966 September 16 (Box 40)
  - Shannon, Sylvia, 1962 August 3 (Box 40)
  - Shaw, Hollie, 1966 September 9 (Box 40)
  - Shearin, Betty F., 1969 December 25 (Box 40)
  - Sheh, Victoria, 1966 June 10 (Box 40)
  - Sheheri, George, 1971 December 15 (Box 40)
  - Shellenberger, Gail, 1962 May 29 (Box 40)
  - Sherin, Mary, 1966 June 24 (Box 40)
  - Sherman, Lee K., 1970 June 26 (Box 40)
  - Shields, Elizabeth, 1968 January 26 (Box 40)
  - Shipley. Emily J., 1969 June 13 (Box 40)
  - Silver, Susan, 1970 February 25 (Box 40)
  - Simmons, Eleanor, 1968 September 6 (Box 40)
  - Simmons, Van, 1971 March 19 (Box 40)
  - Simon, Joel, 1961 August 11 (Box 40)
  - Sinclair, Diane, 1961 May 26 (Box 40)
  - Sirchia, Claire O., 1970 October 2 (Box 40)
  - Sirolly, Margaret, 1967 July 31 (Box 40)
  - Sindelka-Erwin, Jean, 1966 August 25 (Box 40)
  - Skir Ka, Grace, 1961 April 28 (Box 40)
  - Sklarew, Nancy, 1966 April 11 (Box 40)
  - Skolnick, Shelley, 1969 September 1 (Box 40)
  - Skyers, Lillian, 1969 September 15 (Box 40)
  - Slavin, Janet, 1970 June 19 (Box 40)
  - Smakal, Tania, 1969 October 14 (Box 40)
  - Smalls, Mary, 1966 August 19 (Box 40)
  - Smith, Ernest, 1966 September 2 (Box 40)
  - Smulcheski, Peter, 1967 December 15 (Box 40)
  - Snepp, Patricia G., 1969 March 21 (Box 40)
  - Soberman, Miriam, 1966 September 13 (Box 40)
  - Sokol, Dinah, 1961 November 15 (Box 40)
  - Sonnati, Josephine E., 1970 November 13 (Box 40)
  - Sousa, Pilar, 1970 January 30 (Box 40)
  - Span, Robert, 1967 August 25 (Box 40)
  - Speir, Robert (Box 40)
  - Sperber, Bessie, 1958 October 1 (Box 40)
  - Sperling, Susan, 1961 February 3 (Box 40)
  - Spitz, Jill, 1966 May 20 (Box 40)
  - Stagg, Jane, 1970 May 15 (Box 40)
  - Stahl, Susan, 1969 September 30 (Box 40)
  - Stam, Yanick, 1969 September 30 (Box 40)
  - Steginsky, Ethel, 1965 March 3 (Box 40)
  - Stegman, Donna, 1963 June 5 (Box 40)
  - Stephenson, Beth, 1969 January 31 (Box 40)
  - Stephenson, Marvin E. (Box 40)
  - Stevenson, Christine, 1969 January 1 (Box 40)
  - Stollmack, Burton, 1969 January 14 (Box 40)
  - Storch, Susan, 1965 November 1 (Box 40)
  - Stratton, Selby, 1963 August 16 (Box 40)
  - Strobl, Peter, 1968 August 30 (Box 40)
  - Stuart, A. Kristine, 1971 October 29 (Box 40)
  - Sullivan, Brigid, 1970 October 27 (Box 40)
  - Sullivan, Edna, 1970 January 23 (Box 40)
  - Sullivan, Marjorie, 1962 June 29 (Box 40)
  - Sunshine, Carolee, 1965 October 15 (Box 40)
  - Surjador, Paul, 1966 January 14 (Box 40)
  - Svanoe, Atlee, 1965 May 7 (Box 40)
  - Tabert, John F., 1962 August 6 (Box 40)
  - Tadeusiak, Irene, 1969 July 28 (Box 40)
  - Tashjian, Marium G., 1969 September 5 (Box 40)
  - Telfair, Margaret W., 1962 December 31 (Box 40)
  - Ternes, Alan, 1961 June 16 (Box 40)
  - Tharaud, Susan, 1968 July 12 (Box 40)
  - Thomas, Richard, 1965 November 5 (Box 40)
  - Thompson, Karen, 1968 June 21 (Box 40)
  - Thompson, M. Edward, 1970 July 15 (Box 40)
  - Thwaites, Owen, 1970 June 30 (Box 40)
  - Tissot, Jane, 1963 September 30 (Box 40)
  - Tobin, Mary E., 1966 August 12 (Box 40)
  - Tolbert, Natha, 1968 May 31 (Box 40)
  - Tomanek, Susan (formerly Nishijma), 1971 August 13 (Box 40)
  - Torrence Rodney, 1965 June 11 (Box 40)
  - Toufexis, Anastasia, 1966 September 2 (Box 41)
  - Trager, Helen, 1968 September 13 (Box 41)
  - Trigo, Antonio, 1970 May 14 (Box 41)
  - Trimiar, Calvin, 1971 January 29 (Box 41)
  - Tucker, Arthur, 1969 October 24 (Box 41)
  - Tucker, Bernard, 1970 March 21 (Box 41)
  - Tung, Alice, 1965 March 12 (Box 41)
  - Turner, Cathie L., 1970 March 17 (Box 41)
  - Turner, Thomas M., 1966 August 26 (Box 41)
  - Turtle, Mary Lee, 1969 November 26 (Box 41)
  - Underwood, Joanna, 1963 August 2 (Box 41)
  - Urbanski, Charlotte, 1969 September 5 (Box 41)
  - Van Aubel, Catherine, 1961 September 8 (Box 41)
  - Van Buren, Barbara, 1967 November 10 (Box 41)
  - Van Deusen, Charlotte, 1970 November 30 (Box 41)
  - Van Syckle, N. Ray, 1967 February 17 (Box 41)
  - Veale, Thomas, 1959 May 9 (Box 41)
  - Vejarano, Beatriz, 1970 September 11 (Box 41)
  - Velez, Robinson I., 1968 October 15 (Box 41)
  - Veruorrt, Rosemary, 1967 March 10 (Box 41)
  - Vicari, Anne, 1967 February 3 (Box 41)
  - Vincent, Holly, 1971 August 6 (Box 41)
  - Voegelin, Diana, 1960 July 29 (Box 41)
  - Vohland, Judith, 1966 April 13 (Box 41)
  - Wade, Donna, 1968 September 6 (Box 41)
  - Walker, Esther, 1968 May 24 (Box 41)
  - Walker, Robin, 1967 March 3 (Box 41)
  - Wallace, Adelheid, 1965 July 30 (Box 41)
  - Walsh, Mildred L., 1970 May 15 (Box 41)
  - Walton, Rance, 1969 January 15 (Box 41)
  - Warbach, Barbara M., 1967 December 1 (Box 41)
  - Ware, Evan, 1968 May 13 (Box 41)
  - Watts, Susan, 1963 August 26 (Box 41)
  - Waxman, Gayle J., 1968 January 19 (Box 41)
  - Weaver, Janet, 1966 July 1 (Box 41)
  - Weber, Eileen, 1969 October 1 (Box 41)
  - Wegwitz, Friederike U., 1966 June 30 (Box 41)
  - Weiner, Lois F., 1967 December 20 (Box 41)
  - Weiss, Penelope, 1963 December 13 (Box 41)
  - Weiss, Rona, 1971 June 25 (Box 41)
  - Weiss, Vilma, 1967 December 29 (Box 41)
  - Welch, Grace L., 1970 January 23 (Box 41)
  - Werkley, Caroline E., 1965 June 11 (Box 41)
  - Whitcomb, Patricia, 1966 January 31 (Box 41)
  - White, Charlene H., 1966 September 2 (Box 41)
  - Whitney, Clarrissa, 1970 July 31 (Box 41)
  - Whittlesey, Melinda, 1961 June 23 (Box 41)
  - Widenmann, Elizabeth A., 1970 July 17 (Box 41)
  - Wiederhorn, Wendy, 1970 October 9 (Box 41)
  - Widdlesworth, Susan, 1964 August 7 (Box 41)
  - Wilibright, Frank B., 1964 February 28 (Box 41)
  - Wilkins, Toni, 1970 September 18 (Box 41)
  - Williams, Ethel G., 1968 February 16 (Box 41)
  - Williams, Grace Melluain, 1968 December 31 (Box 41)
  - Williams, Richard, 1968 August 30 (Box 41)
  - Williamson, Elizabeth, 1969 March 7 (Box 41)
  - Williamson, Wallace, 1963 August 30 (Box 41)
  - Willis, James, 1966 January 14 (Box 41)
  - Winawer, Lili, 1969 August 15 (Box 41)
  - Winkler, Nancy, 1969 February 19 (Box 41)
  - Winternitz, Ann, 1968 March 4 (Box 41)
  - Winters, Susan, 1968 March 29 (Box 41)
  - Wisely, David, 1965 April 30 (Box 41)
  - Wolf, Margaret B., 1966 September 1 (Box 41)
  - Wood, Peter H. (Box 41)
  - Woodruff, Lois, 1962 August 6 (Box 41)
  - Woods, Josephine, 1969 May 30 (Box 41)
  - Worth, Merwin Braxton, 1962 September 21 (Box 41)
  - Wyatt, Patricia, 1969 July 23 (Box 41)
  - Yarrow, Alene, 1967 September 15 (Box 41)
  - Yeager, Vernon (Box 41)
  - Yett, Diane, 1967 March 10 (Box 41)
  - Young, Mary, 1967 October 31 (Box 41)
  - Youngelman, Bernard, 1964 March 12 (Box 41)
  - Zaloom, Katherine, 1967 November 10 (Box 41)
  - Zavala, Jorge, 1964 April 15 (Box 41)
  - Zeiss, Mary, 1969 April 25 (Box 41)
  - Zimpelman, George, 1965 March 19 (Box 41)
  - Zimtbaum, Nancy, 1961 October 9 (Box 41)
  - Zucker, Stephanie, 1968 May 17 (Box 41)
  - Zuckerman, Frederick (Box 41)
  - Zufic, Blas, 1970 March 31 (Box 41)
  - Student Interns (Box 41)
  - Student Intern - Constantouri, Chris, 1970 February 11 (Box 41)
  - Student Intern - Farsakian, Coharig, 1971 September 6 (Box 41)
  - Student Intern - Ferrer, Maria I., 1971 May 28 (Box 41)
  - Student Intern - Franco, Salvatore, 1971 September 24 (Box 41)
  - Student Intern - Perz, Erika, 1968 September 13 (Box 41)
- Staff, A-Z, Transferred to RAC 1982; 4; 15.77 Cubic Feet 12 record storage boxes
  - Aitken, Thomas H. G. (Box 42)
  - Allen, LeRoy R. (Box 42)
  - Anderson, Charles R. (Box 42)
  - Anderson, Richmond K. (Box 42)
  - Armstrong, Ray E. (Box 42)
  - Arnett, Trevor (Box 42)
  - Arnold, Virginia (Box 42)
  - Arragon, Reginald F. (Box 42)
  - Barnes, Douglas (Box 42)
  - Barry, James W., Jr. (Box 42)
  - Baskett, Ronald S. (Box 42)
  - Beachell, Henry M. (Box 42)
  - Blaser, Roy E. (Box 42)
  - Bonn, George (Box 42)
  - Boshell, Jorge (Box 42)
  - Buckley, Sonja M. (Box 42)
  - Buller, Roderic E. (Box 42)
  - Bunche, Ralph J. (Box 42)
  - Bundy, Emory F. (Box 43)
  - Burden, Robert P. (Box 43)
  - Burress, Charles G. (Box 43)
  - Butwell, Richard L. (Box 43)
  - Cadbury, William (Box 43)
  - Calhoun, Wheeler, Jr. (Box 43)
  - Calkins, Robert D. (Box 43)
  - Callahan, William P. (Box 43)
  - Cameron, Rondo E. (Box 43)
  - Cary, Donald E. (Box 43)
  - Carew, Lyndon B., Jr. (Box 43)
  - Carson, Paul L. (Box 43)
  - Casals-Ariet, Jordi (Box 43)
  - Causey, Ottis R. (Box 43)
  - Chakrabandhu, Prince M. C. (Box 43)
  - Cheng, Ping-yao (Box 43)
  - Christensen, Clyde M. (Box 43)
  - Clark, Paul G. (Box 43)
  - Clarke, Delphine H. (Box 43)
  - Cobb, William C. (Box 43)
  - Compton, Boyd R. (Box 43)
  - Corey, Richard B. (Box 43)
  - Crane, Paul L. (Box 43)
  - Crawford, Robert W. (Box 43)
  - Dalton, Peter (Box 44)
  - D'Arms, Edward F. (Box 44)
  - Davis, Donald E. (Box 44)
  - Davis, Jackson (Box 44)
  - Davis, L. Harlan (Box 44)
  - deRyche, Laurence J. (Box 44)
  - Duff, Ernest A. (Box 44)
  - Dworsky, Leonard B. (Box 44)
  - Eddy, Junius (Box 44)
  - Elguenta, Guerin, Manuel (Box 44)
  - Eltherington, Lorne G. (Box 44)
  - Erickson, Eugene C. (Box 44)
  - Erion, Gerhardt W. (Box 44)
  - Evans, Roger F. (Box 44)
  - Everett, Herbert L. (Box 44)
  - Everton, John Scott (Box 44)
  - Fendall, Neville Rex Edwards (Box 44)
  - Finfrock, Dwight C. (Box 44)
  - Finnerud, Kenneth P. (Box 44)
  - Fireman, Milton (Box 44)
  - Fitzgerald, Paul J. (Box 44)
  - Forshey, Chester G. (Box 44)
  - Forster, Doris B. (Box 44)
  - Fransen, James M. (Box 44)
  - Fraser, Herbert W. (Box 44)
  - Freebairn, Donald K. (Box 45)
  - Freeman, Ruth B. (Box 45)
  - Gibler, John W. (Box 45)
  - Gilpatric, Chadbourne (Box 45)
  - Gleason, L. S. (Box 45)
  - Gordon, Joel E. (Box 45)
  - Greeley, Melvin G. (Box 45)
  - Grevers, John H. (Box 45)
  - Haag, Wayne L. (Box 45)
  - Hagan, Robert M. (Box 45)
  - Hagen, Daniel D. (Box 45)
  - Halpin, James E. (Box 45)
  - Hamlin, Robert H. (Box 45)
  - Hardin, Charles M. (Box 45)
  - Harpstead, Dale D. (Box 45)
  - Harrison, John P. (Box 45)
  - Hatch, James Bliss (Box 46)
  - Hatheway, William H. (Box 46)
  - Heidrick, Lee E. (Box 46)
  - Hellmuth, William F. (Box 46)
  - Henderson, Delbert W. (Box 46)
  - Henderson, Merlin T. (Box 46)
  - Herbert, Geoffrey L. (Box 46)
  - Herdt, Robert W. (Box 46)
  - Hirst, Esther M. (Box 46)
  - Hodgson, Robert W. (Box 46)
  - Holton, Charles S. (Box 46)
  - Huggins, Russell A. (Box 46)
  - Hunter, Thomas H. (Box 46)
  - Janney, John H. (Box 46)
  - Jessup, Philip C. (Box 46)
  - Johnson, Alvin A. (Box 46)
  - Johnson, Joseph C., Jr. (Box 46)
  - Johnson, Lillian A. (Box 46)
  - Jones, John H. (Box 47)
  - Jonkers, Andreis H. (Box 47)
  - Kale, Richard H. (Box 47)
  - Kemp, Graham E. (Box 47)
  - Kennedy, Barbara L. (Box 47)
  - Kerr, J. Austin (Box 47)
  - Knipe, Fred W. (Box 47)
  - Kokernot, Robert H. (Box 47)
  - Krantz, B. A. (Box 47)
  - Krogstad, Blanchard O. (Box 47)
  - Krull, Charles F. (Box 47)
  - Kuttler, Kenneth L. (Box 47)
  - Lambert, Jean W. (Box 47)
  - Leach, Arthur D., Jr. (Box 47)
  - Lee, Vernon H. (Box 47)
  - Lees, Ronald E. M. (Box 47)
  - Leitch, Gordon J. (Box 48)
  - Leitzmann, Claus (Box 48)
  - Lennox, Robert H. (Box 48)
  - Lichti, Frieda Ulrike (Box 48)
  - Lilly, Percy L. (Box 48)
  - Lindsey, Marvin F. (Box 48)
  - Logan, John A. (Box 48)
  - Mackenzie, David R. (Box 48)
  - Mackenzie, Ronald B. (Box 48)
  - Mann, Albert R. (Box 48)
  - Massell, Benton F. (Box 48)
  - Matson, Walter E. (Box 48)
  - McCleary, William A. (Box 48)
  - McCuistion, Willis L. (Box 48)
  - McCune, Donald L. (Box 48)
  - McGowan, Blaine, Jr. (Box 48)
  - McIntosh, Jerry L. (Box 48)
  - McKinley, Erskine W. (Box 48)
  - Mellor, John W. (Box 49)
  - Mercadante, Lucille T. (Box 49)
  - Mikkelsen, Duane S. (Box 49)
  - Moore, Ward W. (Box 49)
  - Morison, Robert S. (Box 49)
  - Morris, Milton E. (Box 49)
  - Mounsey, Irwin (Box 49)
  - Muka, Arthur A. (Box 49)
  - Mullenax, Charles H. (Box 49)
  - Murphy, J. Carter (Box 49)
  - Murphy, Royse P. (Box 49)
  - Nolte, Richard H. (Box 49)
  - Olson, Lloyd C. (Box 49)
  - Orway, Nelson K. (Box 49)
  - Oster, Katharine E. (Box 49)
  - Padgett, L. Vincent (Box 49)
  - Palmer, Louis T. (Box 49)
  - Parson, William (Box 49)
  - Paul, Herbert A. (Box 50)
  - Peck, Marshall H., Jr. (Box 50)
  - Peterson, Arthur E. (Box 50)
  - Peterson, Osler L. (Box 50)
  - Pickett, B. W. (Box 50)
  - Pickett, Robert C. (Box 50)
  - Pope, J. Lon (Box 50)
  - Porter, Wayne M. (Box 50)
  - Powell, Paul E. (Box 50)
  - Prescott, Jon Michael (Box 50)
  - Purks, J. Harris (Box 50)
  - Randall, Frederick E. (Box 50)
  - Raski, Dewey John (D. J.) (Box 50)
  - Rawlins, William A. (Box 50)
  - Ray, Burt (Box 50)
  - Read, Esther H. (Box 50)
  - Reid, J. T. (Box 50)
  - Reitz, J. Wayne (Box 50)
  - Reynolds, Carroll F. (Box 50)
  - Ricker, Albert Stanley (Box 50)
  - Riley, Richard L. (Box 50)
  - Ritcher, Paul O. (Box 50)
  - Roberts, Bill J. (Box 50)
  - Roberts, Edgar Donald (Box 50)
  - Robertson, William Van B. (Box 50)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 50)
  - Robinson, Edward (Box 51)
  - Rodenhiser, Herman A. (Box 51)
  - Rodriquez, Eugene (Box 51)
  - Rogers, Thomas Edwin (Box 51)
  - Romig, Robert W. M. (Box 51)
  - Root, Richard B. (Box 51)
  - Root, Walter S. (Box 51)
  - Ross, Vernon E. (Box 51)
  - Rothchild, Donald S. (Box 51)
  - Runciman, Mildred E. (Box 51)
  - Ruppel, Robert F. (Box 51)
  - Ruttan, Vernon W. (Box 51)
  - Sahs, Warren W. (Box 51)
  - Sandt, Donald G. (Box 51)
  - Sasser, J. N. (Box 51)
  - Saxton, George A., Jr. (Box 51)
  - Sayre, Kenneth D. (Box 51)
  - Schafer, David E. (Box 51)
  - Shaffer Carol Marie (Box 51)
  - Shepherd, George W., Jr. (Box 51)
  - Skiles, Robert L. (Box 51)
  - Slack, Samuel T. (Box 51)
  - Smith, Donald L. (Box 51)
  - Smith, Richard M. (Box 51)
  - Soto, Pablo E. (Box 51)
  - Sprague, Lucian M. (Box 51)
  - Stewart, Jane R. (Box 52)
  - Stonaker, Howard H. (Box 52)
  - Streeter, Carroll P. (Box 52)
  - Sturrock, Robert F. (Box 52)
  - Sunde, Milton L. (Box 52)
  - Swope, Robert E. (Box 52)
  - Thomas, Leo A. (Box 52)
  - Thomas, Robert M. (Box 52)
  - Thompson, Roy L. (Box 52)
  - Thurston, H. David (Box 52)
  - Timothy, David H. (Box 52)
  - Towne, Dudley H. (Box 52)
  - Trapido, Harold (Box 52)
  - Traywick, Jack D. (Box 52)
  - Turner, Thomas E. (Box 52)
  - Tyner, Edward H. (Box 52)
  - Ullstrup, Arnold J. (Box 52)
  - Upatham, Edward S. (Box 52)
  - Usenik, Edward A. (Box 52)
  - Van Dyke, George E. (Box 52)
  - Vavich, Mitchell G. (Box 52)
  - Veenstra, John G. (Box 53)
  - Webb, Hubert E. (Box 53)
  - West, Robert L. (Box 53)
  - Westerberg, Nils J. (Box 53)
  - Whitman, Loring (Box 53)
  - Wiersma, Daniel (Box 53)
  - Wilcoxson, Roy D. (Box 53)
  - Williams, Greer (Box 53)
  - Williams, Roger W. (Box 53)
  - Wilson, Ruby L. (Box 53)
  - Winegar, Elizabeth Ann (Box 53)
  - Woodall, John P. (Box 53)
  - Work, Telford H. (Box 53)
  - Worth, C. Brooke (Box 53)
  - Yates, Vance J. (Box 53)
  - Yeager, Vernon L. (Box 53)
  - Young, M. Crawford (Box 53)
- Former Professional Staff, Transferred to RAC 1982; 5; 5.26 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
  - Anderson, Robert G. (Box 54)
  - Balfour, Marshall C. (Box 54)
  - Bourne, Leo F. (Box 54)
  - Bradfield, Richard (Box 54)
  - Buchanan, Norman S. (Box 54)
  - Bugher, John C. (Box 54)
  - Cole, Charles W. (Box 54)
  - Fahs, Charles B. (Box 54)
  - Fletcher, Donald G. (Box 54)
  - Gillette, H. Malcolm (Box 54)
  - Golden, William G. (Box 54)
  - Grant, Mrs. Charlotte H. (Box 55)
  - Grant, John B. (Box 55)
  - Grant, Mrs. Magdalan L. (Box 55)
  - Gray, George W. (Box 55)
  - Heins, William A. (Box 55)
  - Hill, Rolla B. (Box 55)
  - Kumm, Henry W. (Box 55)
  - Letoit, Robert (Box 55)
  - Magoon, Estus H. (Box 55)
  - Marshall, John (Box 56)
  - Mason, Max (Box 56)
  - McCloy, Oliver R. (Box 56)
  - Miller, Harry M., Jr. (Box 56)
  - Myers, Will M. (Box 56)
  - Oliver, Wade (Box 56)
  - Oughterson, Ashley W. (Box 56)
  - Paine, Janet M. (Box 56)
  - Painter, Reginald H. (Box 56)
  - Pomerat, Gerard R. (Box 56)
  - Pomeroy, Charles R. (Box 56)
  - Porter, Wayne W. (Box 56)
  - Rey, C. F. (Box 56)
  - Rhind, Flora (Box 56)
  - Rogers, Daniel C. (Box 56)
  - Russell, Paul F. (Box 57)
  - Sadun, Elvin H. (Box 57)
  - Smithburn, Kenneth C. (Box 57)
  - Stakman, E. C. (Box 57)
  - Staff Candidates, 1960s (Box 57)
  - Steel, Rowe S. (Box 57)
  - Struthers, R. Rolf (Box 57)
  - Theiler, Max (Box 57)
- Field Staff and Former Staff, Transferred to RAC 1982; 6; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
  - Brooks, Glenn E. (Box 58)
  - Chalmers, James A. (Box 58)
  - Coppock, Joseph D. (Box 58)
  - Daniel, James M. (Box 58)
  - Fitchett, Delbert A. (Box 58)